This time it's pets against wilds. Wiener takes all!
Open Season 2 is a adventure, animation, comedy
film directed by Matthew O'Callaghan.
After falling head over hooves in love with Giselle, Elliot's
road to the altar takes a slight detour when Mr.
Weenie is kidnapped by a group of pampered pets
determined to return him to his owners.
Elliot (Voice), played by Joel McHale.
Boog (Voice), played by Mike Epps.
Mr. Weenie (voice), played by Cody Cameron.
Bobbie (voice), played by Georgia Engel.
Giselle (Voice), played by Jane Krakowski.
McSquizzy (voice), played by Billy Connolly.
Open Season 2 is a 2008 American animated comedy film and
the second in the Open Season film series.
It was directed by Matthew O'Callaghan.
It premiered theatrically in South Africa on September 24, 2008, and was
released direct-to-video in the United States on January 27, 2009.
The film received mixed reviews and grossed $8.7 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of deer, sequel, bear, dog, animals.
The tone is lighthearted.